All right. Hello, everyone. Adrian Agdan here. You can call me Ryan for short.
So here's the quick demo for the AI Voice Receptionist that we created by the help of Claude, of course.
And let me explain you the whole system and the visual map.
So first, this is the full flow. As you can see, patient fills up the form.
And after five seconds, boom, it will receive an AI call from Vapi.
Appointment will be booked in the CRM.
So under the hood, we are going to use HighLevel as the CRM captures the form, triggers the automation.
And then is the brain in the middle. It connects everything.
It fires the outbound call, handle errors, and logs the data.
And for the Vapi, that's Emma. It's going to be our outbound voice AI.
And she's not reading from a script.
She's thinking. She calls the patient, has a real conversation, and actually checks HighLevel, real-time calendar.
And also Superbase, everything gets logged in here.
Transcript, recording, information, outcome, sentiment, and the full audit trail.
So the reasoning of our receptionist is GPT-40 mini, Deepgram for the voice and listening.
And here for the data trail, after the end of the call, you'll have the appointment, internal notes,
and internal comment on the CRM side, and Superbase for the calls, role, contacts, and appointments.
AI analysis for the outcome sentiment, cost of the Vapi call, and the transcript.
And yeah, so let me show you how this works live.
So let's go ahead and go to the form as the initial entry of our flow.
All right.
So let me click Submit from here.
And as you can see, it should run on high level on NNN.
And let me quickly prepare my phone here.
All right.
I received the call after a few seconds.
So let me just press any key to connect.
Press any key here.
Hi, Mark.
This is Emma from Riley Coptic Surgery.
I saw the form you just submitted about breast augmentation.
Let us get you booked for a free discovery call with Dr. Riley Smith right now.
I have a few slots available.
Do you prefer mornings or afternoons?
Afternoon work for me.
The nearest opening I have is on Monday, June 8th.
I have slots available at 11 a.m., 12 p.m., or 1 p.m. Pacific time.
Would one of those work?
Do any of those hands work for you?
8 a.m.?
Of course.
Let me find another option for you.
The next available times on Monday, June 8th, are 11 a.m., 12 p.m., or 1 p.m. Pacific time.
Would one of those work?
How about 1 p.m.?
Great.
Just to confirm, we'll schedule your free discovery call for Monday, June 8th at 1 p.m. Pacific time.
Is that correct?
No.
Can we do Wednesday instead?
I'm sorry.
Of course.
Let me find another option for you.
I'll check the availability for Wednesday, June 10th.
One moment, please.
I have found an opening on Wednesday, June 10th at 12 p.m. Pacific time.
Would you like me to book that for you?
All right.
Yes, I think that's fine.
I can do that.
Perfect, Mark.
Your free discovery call is confirmed for Wednesday, June 10th at 12 p.m. Pacific time.
You will receive a confirmation shortly.
If you have any questions or need assistance before then, feel free to reach out.
Have a great day.
You too have a great day.
Bye.
Thank you, Mark.
Have a wonderful day.
All right.
So here, let me check the CRM.
Let's see if Emma really books our appointment.
And all right.
The account was created under Mark Mas.
It's the same name on the form.
Let's see the CRM, how it looks like.
Okay.
So it seems like it created an opportunity and also an internal comment that we are interested
in the best augmentation and the summary of what we just talked about, which is changing
the day, the time, and ultimately agreed to June 10th at 12 p.m.
So let's check the appointment here.
So here, yeah, I can see it's correct, which is June 10th, 12 p.m. to 1 p.m. Pacific time.
That's great.
So let's go ahead and check now the CRM or the Superbase real quick if it's noted there.
Okay.
Let me show you the most recent one here.
Yeah.
So you can see under appointment table, you will be able to see here the schedule, appointment
ID, calendar ID, schedule time, duration of the call, and other information.
So you can see the name here under markmask.
That's our name.
And if you're going to go to the calls, you will see the information from Vapi as well
that the status was completed, the full transcript of our call, and the summary and other information
that will be really useful for our metrics.
And also the contact name will be here under contacts, the name, phone number, email, GHL
ID, and other important information as well.
So yeah, it perfectly shows us the database as well that it really works.
And yeah, that's it.
And hope that I'll be able to help you with your automation needs as well.
Thank you so much for watching.
Have a good one.
Bye-bye.